This is your "special place"?
Yeah.
The place you can get the most excited
and power up the most.
But...
Okay, class is starting.
Be quiet.
Okay!
Class?
Why?
W-Wait...
We're in the middle of class,
so you should be quiet.
S-Stop it...
Not here! No way!
You're too loud.
What if they notice?
"What if they notice"?
Just don't do this, then!
Stop it!
You're kidding...
N-No!
This is the finishing blow!
Next is Chidorigafuchi.
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
Oh, no! They'll see!
Come on, solve the problem.
O-Okay.
Hey, look.
Is she not wearing panties?
Are you serious?
Everybody's watching.
So is Kizuna.
So why...
Why am I so excited?
Why do I feel so good?!
Unimaginable embarrassment
will bring out Aine's power.
Okay, that's all for today.
You're such a dummy!
I was so embarrassed!
Yeah, you did great.
Just a little more.
Aine?
Episode 13
Aine -Aines-
Aren't Aine-san and Kizuna-kun
taking a little too long?
You don't get to talk, Hayuru.
Jeez...
Sylvia, how's it going over there?
Oh, stop it, Captain...
Sylvia?
That girl is having a very nice dream.
Who are you?
Is it finally time for the last boss?
Neros and Kuros?
It seems you've been giving our
expeditionary forces a hard time.
So I'll let you have a very special dream.
Heart Rebuild.
I-I was trying to hold back my embarrassment,
and now I'm at my limit!
If I move, it's going to drip out!
I see.
So let me go to the bathroom.
Kizuna?
Leave it to me.
What's going on?
I brought them all here...
...to watch you Climax Hybrid.
Y-You're kidding!
I'm serious.
No...
N-No!
S...
S-Stop it!
Don't look! Don't look at me!
Th-This is too much...
Any more and I won't be able to hold it!
You don't have to.
Expose your true self.
I-I can't.
Too embarrassing!
Don't worry.
I'm next to you.
Kizuna!
I can't...
No!
Okay.
Climax Hybrid!
Is that...
...the light of my Immoral Weapon?
Aine?
No!
Aine? Hang in there, Aine!
I...
Aine, are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
My hair's still silver?
Did the Climax Hybrid fail?
I'm sorry.
I thought it would work for sure.
It's my fault.
Aine.
I was about to get this incredible power,
but I was too scared.
Don't blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
Kizuna!
What...
No!
Himekawa!
Yurishia!
Sylvia!
It's useless.
Who's there?
Captain of the Batlantis Empire's
Royal Guards, Zelshione.
Your cries won't reach them.
Their souls are currently floating
deep within their minds.
Wh-What did you say?!
Where am I?!
Where are you, everyone?!
Tri-Head.
You're so awful...
Why didn't you save me?
I didn't want to die...
You're a liar!
No...
Liar!
I tried t-to save you...
Just hang in there, everyone.
I'm on my way.
That's...
N... No way...
Scarlet...
Everyone, I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
They're swallowed up by a nightmare.
A past that might have been,
filled with pain and regrets.
What?
So a psychological attack, basically?
A cowardly, shameful way of fighting
without getting your hands dirty!
Your complaints don't even reach my ears.
You never had a chance.
Scarlet!
Sharon!
Henrietta!
It's no good!
The bitches aren't answering me!
What happened?
Reiri...
A new Magitech weapon attack on Area 11!
Counterattack system crippled!
I'll show you what the Masters can do!
Up our pay while you're at it!
Hang in there, and Amaterasu will...
The Eros Overlord will do something.
If you surrender to the Batlantis Empire,
I'll spare your lives.
What?
Even you Lemurians have value...
...as cattle for harvesting life energy.
How about it? I promise you a happy life.
Shut up!
How could I be happy if
I stopped being myself?
Kizuna...
That girl doesn't seem to
know who she is, though.
Where did you get the Zeros core?
Don't tell me you've forgotten.
Where?
It's got nothing to do with you!
Even if I knew I wouldn't tell you!
Wh-What is this?
Aine!
Then...
...I'll have you go find where you got it,
by going back through your own memories!
Bring back Aine.
Bring back everyone!
You're just a man.
Did you think you could lay a finger on me?
I'll make you pay...
I'll make you pay for this!
Eros!
Where am I supposed to go?
You're going to look for the core, right?
I see.
That's why I'm here, isn't it?
So the core's already been installed?
Already been installed?
Is this...
Take this!
Move!
You're in the way!
I should've known an
incomplete Climax Hybrid
wouldn't give me enough power!
He fights for those he loves?
How long will he last?
What is that?
Damn it!
Are you really sure?
The truth lies beyond this door.
But once you open it, there's no going back.
Are you sure?
I don't...
I don't know what to do.
Why are you crying?
I'm not done yet...
At this rate...
Zeros Mode!
Bring everyone back!
How interesting.
I had no idea such a Magitech armor existed.
I'll have to take my time
investigating it later.
A man's screams can be pretty pleasant, too!
This was at least a little entertaining.
I'm not done yet...
I swore I'd save them all...
That I wouldn't let them die...
That I'd protect them.
And that's why I...
You're not needed anymore.
That's why I'm here!
What's this?
I know.
You're always with me.
We're with you, too.
So feel us as much as you can.
Please use Sylvia!
Now, then...
You don't know when to give up.
Kizuna-kun!
Kizuna!
Captain!
Eros!
Wh-What?
Amaterasu Mode!
Eros's Hybrid Count is rising!
That sumbitch Kizuna's in top form!
But he hasn't done a Heart Hybrid.
Pleasure and excitement
without even touching?
Ecstasy that goes beyond the body.
Carnality between minds
calling to one another.
This is the ultimate form of love.
A miracle has just occurred!
Go!
Neros!
Kuros!
Taros!
Go!
You're all that's left!
Don't underestimate me!
How about some last words after that scream—
I laid more than a finger on you.
Y-You...
How dare you do that to my Teros?
Everyone!
I'm glad...
When...
You're the first person to push me this far.
I'll give you my praise for that.
As a reward,
I'll have her finish you!
Aine...
I'll think about it with you!
That's right.
Kizuna was protecting me, even then.
But I got scared and ran.
Maybe it's not too late.
Wh-What is this?
No! This isn't...
Stop it!
Stop!
Aine-san, what are you—?!
Stop! Aine!
Don't!
Kizuna! Kizuna! Kizuna!
I want to feel you!
With my hands, with my body,
with everything I am!
I want to hold you!
I want to become one with you!
So I want power!
Welcome back, me.
Aine?
She's back?
Zeros.
Th-That can't be...
Th-The Forbidden...
You!
Aine, I'll...
...protect you!
Code Breaker.
My Gear?
I-I can't go down here!
What happened?
The sealing system!
Th-The magical power is disappearing!
The Magitech signal of the
Entrance is dropping rapidly!
The sealing system is activating!
The Entrance is gone!
The operation was a goddamn success!
Well done.
Reiri.
Good work.
You, too.
Nayuta-sama, what is this?
Well done, Aine.
Now we can proceed to
the next phase of the experiment.
Aine?
What is this?
Forget it.
I'm just glad you're safe.
Kizuna.
Aine-san!
Kizuna!
Captain!
Guys!
It's so beautiful.
Yeah.
Princess of the Batlantis Empire,
Aines Sinclavia.
Sister!